

Kateřina Hrubá

DESIGNER

ABOUT

I am a graphic and media design student. I consider myself to be open-minded, creative, and with a sense of punctuality. I am passionate about all forms of art but mostly about design and photography. I think of myself as a positive and communicative person with a sense of empathy. I have no problem working in a team and I am always excited to learn new things. I'm a hard worker and I don't like to do things at the last minute.

I enjoy traveling and getting to know other cultures and people. During my high school studies, I traveled abroad twice for half a year. First I spent 6 months in the US where I attended high school in Colorado. Two years later I visited Australia. Both of these experiences thought me independence, problem-solving ability, and the ability to work in a multicultural setting.

One of my other passions in life is swimming so don't be surprised when you run into me with wet hair.

SKILLS

I can work with most of the programs in Adobe creative suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, Indesign, Xd, Lighroom, Premier).
I try to look outside the box with every one of my projects and I think the key to a success in the field of graphic design is communication between the designer and the client.
Also, I am capable of producing product pictures or lifestyle pictures for proffesional or personal use.

LANGUAGES

Czech - native
English - proficient, C1
Spanish - Intermediate
French - beginner

EXPERIENCE

June 2020- Present

Wedding factory

Part-time wedding arranger and designer

Designing and arranging wedding venues.

Responsible for decorations and design. Part-time coordinating weddings. Coordinating guests and everyone involved in the wedding.

January 2020-June 2020

Magazine Šestka

Internship-External designer

External designer for a magazine at Prague 6. Work involved designing posters and infographics for Prague 6.

January 2019-May 2019

Swim&relax shop

Part-time saleswoman

A part-time job at a shop with swimming equipment.
Selling swimming equipment at Podolí swimming
pool. Also included receiving goods, processing
e-shop orders, and inventory counting.

Summer 2017, Summer 2018, Summer 2019

Sara MB

lifeguard

Working at an outdoor swimming pool as a summer job. Included having a lifeguard course.

EDUCATION

2018- Currently studying (3rd year)

VŠKK,Prague

Graphic and media design specialization.

A three-year study programme with bachelor degree.

2010-2018

GMVV, Prague

Eight-year high school specialized in languages and international relations.